NLRB Oral History Project II Transcripts 5843 OHT
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB Oral History Project II Transcripts
1987-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
Gross, James
5843 OHT
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Interviews, transcripts.
5713645
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 12, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /3013: Christopher Lindley Papers /3036: Robert Raimon Papers /3051: Albert Martin Papers /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4040: George H. Hildebrand Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James A. Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4064: Kurt Hanslowe Papers /4073: James O. Morris Office Files /4085: Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes /4117 P: ILR School Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4148: George W. Brooks Additional Papers /4162: Kheel Center Additional Special Projects Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4166 AV: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Audio-Visual Materials /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4191 F: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Films /4212: Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4232: James A. Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4256: ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials 5011: Morton Singer Papers 5016: Cornell University Union Representation Material 5034: Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5073: U.S. Board of Inquiry to Report on Certain Labor Disputes Affecting the Maritime Industry of the United States Records 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm
Gross, James.; United States. National Labor Board.
5713645
- Lester Asher, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Transcript no.1147. October 14, 1988
- Norton Come, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Transcript no.1148. July 29, 1988
- Warren Davison, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Transcript no.1149. August 08, 1988
- Francis A. OConnell, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Transcript no.1150. May 23, 1987
- Joseph DeSio, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Transcript no.1151. August 02, 1988
- William Feldesman, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Transcript no.1152. July 28, 1988
- Stephen Gordon, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Transcript no.1153. August 01, 1988
- John E. Higgins, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Transcript no.1154. July 26, 1988
- Howard Jenkins, Jr., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Transcript no.1155. August 09, 1988
- Theophil Kammholz and Kenneth McGuiness, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Transcript no.1156. Two interviews in folder. McGuiness interview, August 01, 1988. Kammholz interview, October 13, 1988
- Frank Kleiler, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Transcript no.1157. August 03, 1988
- Marcel Mallet-Prevost, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Transcript no.1158. August 04, 1988
- Frank McCulloch, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Transcript no.1159. September 05, 1989
- Kenneth McGuiness, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Transcript no.1160. August 01, 1988
- Thomas W. Miller, Jr., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Transcript no.1161. September 08, 1989
- Peter Nash, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Transcript no.1162. July 27, 1988
- Daniel H. Pollitt, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Transcript no.1163. September 07, 1989
- Roman Pucinski, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Transcript no.1164. October 13, 1988
- Mozart Ratner, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Transcript no.1165. July 25, 1988
- A. Norman Somers, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Transcript no.1166. August 01, 1988
- Stanley R. Strauss, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Transcript no.1167. August 12, 1988
- Berton Subrin, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Transcript no.1168. August 05, 1988
- John Truesdale, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Transcript no.1169. August 02, 1988
- Michael Walsh, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Transcript no.1170. January 11, 1989
- Ralph Winkler, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Transcript no.1171. August 04, 1988
- Sam Zagoria, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Transcript no.1172. August 09, 1988
- Melvin Welles, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Transcript no.1173. July 27, 1988
- Gerald Brown, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Transcript no.1174. May 26, 1987
- Gerald Brown, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Douglas Soutar, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Transcript no.1175. November 16, 1990
- Lester Asher, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Transcript no.1147 (copy 2). October 14, 1988
- Norton Come, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Transcript no.1148 (copy 2). July 29, 1988
- Warren Davison, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Transcript no.1149 (copy 2). August 08, 1988
- Francis A. OConnell, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Transcript no.1150 (copy 2). May 23, 1987
- William Feldesman, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Transcript no.1152 (copy 2). July 28, 1988
- Stephen Gordon, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Transcript no.1153 (copy 2). August 01, 1988
- John E. Higgins, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Transcript no.1154 (copy 2). July 26, 1988
- Howard Jenkins, Jr., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Transcript no.1155 (copy 2). August 09, 1988
- Theophil Kammholz and Kenneth McGuiness, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Transcript no.1156 (copy 2). Two interviews in folder. McGuiness interview, August 01, 1988. Kammholz interview, October 13, 1988
- Frank Kleiler, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Transcript no.1157 (copy 2). August 03, 1988
- Marcel Mallet-Prevost, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Transcript no.1158 (copy 2). August 04, 1988
- Kenneth McGuiness, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Transcript no.1160 (copy 2). August 01, 1988
- Peter Nash, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Transcript no.1162 (copy 2). July 27, 1988
- Roman Pucinski, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Transcript no.1164 (copy 2). October 13, 1988
- Mozart Ratner, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Transcript no.1165 (copy 2). July 25, 1988
- Stanley R. Strauss, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Transcript no.1167 (copy 2). August 12, 1988
- Berton Subrin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Transcript no.1168 (copy 2). August 05, 1988
- John Truesdale, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Transcript no.1169 (copy 2). August 02, 1988
- Michael Walsh, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Transcript no.1170 (copy 2). January 11, 1989
- Ralph Winkler, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Transcript no.1171 (copy 2). August 04, 1988
- Sam Zagoria, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Transcript no.1172 (copy 2). August 09, 1988
- Melvin Welles, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Transcript no.1173 (copy 2). July 27, 1988